Please remember,
don't know if it's necessary either. There was no seal.
Remember that night, meditate in a group. It's
very important to eat your fill.
Inga, let's start.
And there's a galaxy far away. Please
relax your forehead.
Biloxi, Mom, please, the cone grew past,
especially the corners of the mouth. Choki, down, water. This,
check your fingers. Are they
tense or not? With there, and did it bring you
a little inward? Your stomach and
faces are relaxed.
Your eyeballs are relaxed.
Your forehead should be relaxed. Your eyelids are
relaxed.
Land, with a search, like,
please, start breathing. Lome, access is
long. You did it like that. Stepping,
please, exhale the maximum
amount of air from your lungs.
Black robe b5 and look. You're engaged in darkness. It would
simply be practically
glued to your breath so that they
touch very tightly. Breathing and
consciousness,
you don't give up. Chuck, Kandil, synapse, main.
Please, check the state of yours.
Created
turmoil. Books on the sea. If you have it in the
morning. Your nose is for war. It's cool with Sobchak
and you might. Please, check all. I
confess. Sages.  How calm is the whole
city? How quiet is it? But it's located
on 1 kilometer of zinc and they took it away. The
guests are asking now. Please
think about your friend who is very close to you and
our wise foundation.
We have people who
produce gas and make a special impression on you. We
conducted tests. Power. They do very
well. They were filmed for life on their other
people. They say very good words. They are
similar to other people.
They are very friendly, raw, not very
respectful. They drew from this. They are a
guarantor for other people.
You always have to be a fence. Please
go through your friends' list. Break
one and choose one. At the end of the year, shame.
Aquas. You have a mass interval from who
will sit opposite today. The video from
your teacher's place affected us and we will see from
or a request to yours. You are sitting opposite a
good friend and just a good
person.
Enc Akimat. I think they have an antigen and now it will
sag.
How calm is your homeland? Did the
lakes harm you and check your disk.
Your heart will achieve this. Check how you breathe. The
yard is very different. Does the water surface change
after you planted in front of it?
with your good friend to
meditate with you
and the
backpack nose we also have
friends who will put the pieces
positively
the bottom manifests itself in their lives those
who are not very good and put them behind
talking to people maybe they are
a little of this arrow
spin the bottle but we still spend
our time with this I agree with subtract, would
I like to ask you now to
change the person who meditated
with me girl on a view Frenchman over and
invite him to meditation one person
who is not very respectful best tore apart
terin life Nazis let him
start with you we will create and and look at the
marriage the surface of your lake will
change how much the vase will change
your heartbeat please
check this defense products if there is
any difference because with Mr. View
Maine not the state of your consciousness and in
how you breathe how blue and cold
heart role when these two people
are in your environment
noofen senora and New Mexico when
designing
tonight please in that house
where you life of people today after dinner
when you  You will be alone in the room number
this fish cliff and you do not have this you
do not meditate you just relax in a
quarrel logo
but I feel maybe you enjoy
the surroundings, well, there is a very
beautiful sunset here people
cheese and you just sit until qnet I go out you
look out the window the sun and watch the
sunset
year main
brands of beer how at this moment the
surface of consciousness of your router feels
what is your heartbeat at this moment
but I will sing and the final part
please Latin prices all that you now
have to do your in the union Kamal
think about what you will do
when you return home on the next
ringing what you should do your
responsibility maybe you have to
pay money from the account
some tasks in your work compression
tag itself done
try to think about some of these
conveniences and hobbies and see how it
modifies our for evil my yard and
thinks how your heart beats this is how the
surface of the water in your
lake consciousness changes
dentis compacte mania mindami us
now please return to the
state of consciousness when you  Powder just
woke up
when you closed your meditation this morning
when your state of mind was
calm and peaceful
young access please take three
long exhalations the
cop understands again so slowly
open your eyes and apologize
binks on the loop please something
guys do you have a microphone ready does anyone
of you want degrees when in the morning in the form of
love tomatoes positive your life
and you saw a friend who is not very
put how your breathing changed how it
changed not even the beginning of the heart as the
surface consciousness lake changed with
your consciousness someone wants to say about this
please good morning side by side by
side
boker tov this is in Hebrew good morning I
couldn't find a friend whom I don't
like in this life you are very happy and the
states of everyone you don't have friends who
irritate you but also I couldn't
find a person whom I could
call a friend the hero of the middle means you do
n't need laurels
but I really saw that the way
I breathe changes
really I breathed much faster and
really my heartbeat increased
burned out anyone else please
firstly somehow my consciousness was
peaceful I was here such an
impression  that there were no thoughts at all
and the water was calm
then I was opposite my good
friend
I was smiling inside me it was like
such a sunny state then I
thought about a person a person who is not
so good and I was in such a
state as if I was expecting something as
if something bad should happen I was
constantly monitoring and checking what
she would do
has begun
at first I was in a state of
absolute calm
then I thought about a person who is not
very good in my life I had
such heavy breathing I felt
heaviness inside me and then when we
changed the state I was on my own my
state changed everything
calmed down
and when you said I need to go home to
return to tasks then my
breathing changed dramatically thank you very much
or broth anyone else
just than and and
[music]
thank you for the wonderful experience
when I was in a state
that in Daimon Mountain I was in a
peaceful state the
water was very calm but when I
thought about a person I
like it seems that the water has become
warmer it seems that I feel better
it is very much
when I thought a little uncomfortable
In my life, my water became
a little colder and it was no longer
so calm, some waves appeared,
and then when I thought that I
should go to my, I realized that I did
n’t want to go home at all, there were so many things to do at
home, Bugatti
life,
thank you teacher for your teaching, every
time I come here and being here with you, these are
just happy moments in my
life. When I felt I thought that
I needed to go home, I became nervous
about the fact that there was so much to
do at home, when you asked and invited a
good person, a good friend, Ginny
came into my consciousness
from I asked Jenny if she was my
best friend, and my state was
very calm at that moment,
because when we are all in the 10th
round, we are all like one family, we
all help each other, maybe that’s why
I planted these seeds of
friendship when I meditated on Ginny, but
when I invited a not very good
friend, Tula,
I remembered what a person came to
my company, then this person left
this company, and I was in such a
state of disappointment,
and then I realized that the one who is a true
friend  and I thought that this real friend
turns out to be this and not the real friend of
my life that
I was thinking about, thank you, unfortunately, my
morning state of consciousness is very sleepy
but calm
when I thought about my good friend, my
best friend,
but my state of mind was also very
enthusiastic, how glad I am to see you, let's
do something together, and the water
just started jumping when I thought about a
person who is not the best friend in
my life or a person who is not so
good in my life, I felt that
my state of consciousness was
freezing and the water was freezing, I
felt very
suffering, I had the feeling that there was a
wall between us and I was knocking on this
wall, trying to reach this
person, I was just suffering, daytime prison,
apparently I took more
coffee than I should today, she said,
coffee is your friend, or how it feels like this
irritation doesn't
go away at all and I won't take coffee in the morning
before a party anymore, but I would
s.i.
thanks for the teaching
I am very glad I was glad to be with my friend
it was very calm then I
thought about my company and my heart
right away got drunk with a mouse envy
such a feeling that the heart like a machine
just beat strongly
and consciousness became restless the water was
absolutely restless opaque and
when I thought about what would be the
sunset edges in which for some reason
my heart did not feel the keys are not important
opened with a screwdriver
I wanted to say that I just he
feels good when I thought the past few
days it felt like I took
more coffee than necessary I tried to
calm down in the presence of my good
friend they helped me a lot I had a
feeling of warmth and I calmed down and when I
generally invited a person who is not
very good in life I will not call him a friend I
had a feeling of cold I had a
feeling as if I was involved
in some very strong problem and I
could not understand where this problem comes from
then when I returned already in a
state of calm but it was a calm and
satisfied state
it was such an ecstatic
state that is, I really wanted to
quickly accept into life and use in
Life, everything I've learned here these days,
and thank you so much for what I've
learned. You have this feeling that you're
working, who's there,
that is, someone enters the room, a
trailer, he enters the room, a problem
today with whom, a conflict in a new state,
what he holds it for a long
time, I now want to talk about one
monk,
your consciousness, the
first 100 people, or simply because of
which it
accelerates today, a state of rest of the mind
becomes unstable, tucker, and this is as
if preliminary and a state that you have
lost balance, then you have
irritation,
you haven't said anything, you've
already gotten angry and ordered,
and then this creates scorched
owls, keep in your mind chapters, but Windows,
Adobe, what we called in the last
approach to being girls,
what music for beginners, myself, here is the radio,
Voitov school, they say, wish, then you
just need to avoid, avoid contact with what
you have with donuts, this is not the best method
for getting better than it can be,
for example, not meeting millions, this is
not easy, she has moments, someone will talk about them,
this is called object 2, this is a little,
I'm now Hussarov, this is a person who is
Hambo today, naturally  reality, he is
very attentive and very caring, he
works very carefully, he also does
the accounting for us and leads many
projects, but he leads this is great, is it
in a sauna when you are around this person of
your gift, consciousness is very calm, you
feel the need for hands, and when you find
someone irritates you who says
bad words, Berg and Rome fax, it’s like it infects
you, they infect your consciousness,
your behavior, it increases with speed,
there is a tradition in Omsk, it didn’t come together,
brought try not to be surrounded,
try to be surrounded by good people,
several people said that bad
friends are in your life, please
be careful, more time,
behavior, do not try to absolutely
endorse spending time with bad
people,
will you be with them no matter how long you are with them,
they will be consciousness 1, this
harness says that I avoid the
city founded on thin ice, for example, hung up
Nidalzho to give birth and buy racers for myself, I
should generally not be very strong, but I
tried 5 Spider Man, there is such an aroma,
but it spreads throughout the airport, and it
seems to me this is the second round, what were they talking about,
good words for Aldo, so that it
means something, just a
lot  What hurts is a lot of coffee, a lot of
biplanes, a lot of thoughts. This is a very well
-known word, and it will change, it
means, and right now, a gram. Here, right now, and
my recording, that Eldzhey himself is more for negative
emotions, this is our
busy consciousness, except, unfortunately,
together, once a good town, we have
an interview on it, we
can study yoga, a gift, we can find
thousands of classes on the Internet for
free. I'm used to it, it's excellent, but the other
side of the Internet constantly keeps
your consciousness thinking, grabbing, and
negative emotions just
love to grow, like in this
back behind our head, you have such a michel,
as if you're running some kind of race, your
heart doesn't increase, your breathing,
and that's it.  As you know, it's
fertile for you to have
negative emotions once in a while, when
this
negative object that enters the room of the
list, it turns out you see this yoga
very easily at this moment you can
become one of the generally every now and then and
managed in the subject center of whom it is to
create varnish conditions for dust in contact
with the fact that you were surrounded by good people,
usually bad people do not come other than
house 12
and thirdly, this is your home, you are not here like that
eyes, but if you do not take into account that now there are
trainers of teachers of the whole disk, a candle
with you talked about three
irritating elements lies down, know,
we will not read more, please, well,
go for and at home irritants of your
life because people